[music]
>> Wait,
that's not fair. How come regular
Kristen gets to bring in her kid, but I
can't bring in my pet snake? Maybe
because when you did it laid eggs in
Collette's floppy purse. Yeah, and they
looked a lot like yogurt-covered
almonds.
>> Mhm. Good morning.
First off, happy birthday Kristen. Aw,
cheers Kristen. Sorry, which Kristen?
Hot Chris.
Young Chris.
That one?
Blonde. You get to wear the birthday
pin.
Um can I just leave early instead? No.
Now, Big Sec sent us some awesome new
swag.
>> Yay! Lame. Lame. Now, to remind us to
stay healthy during cold and flu season.
Everybody, meet Huey the hygiene
raccoon.
>> Oh, that makes zero sense. Raccoons are
literally filthy. They eat out of the
garbage. Mary, she loves raccoons. She
calls them trash pandas. [laughter]
Oh my god, that's so funny. Did she come
up with that herself?
>> [laughter]
>> Amazing.
Girl, tighten up. Yeah. You know what
reminds me to stay healthy, Barb? Tell
me, Greg. The fact that we only have
three paid sick days per year. Speaking
of full disclose, my pinworms are back.
Highly contagious.
Yeah.
I got cooties.
>> [music]
>> You're a couple, no? Oh my god. I'm just
kidding. They're both super cringe.
So, what are you going to do?
I don't know. There's nothing to do.
I guess I could focus on me. Oh my god,
you are such a white girl. Mhm.
I guess I can hop on my Zoom with my
therapist, or I can go grab my weighted
blanket and eat Greek yogurt on the
couch for some hashtag self-care. Oh,
better yet, I'll log onto a neighborhood
app and give my two cents to make sure
everybody else heard the scary noise I
heard in the middle of the night.
You're way off. I couldn't begin to move
my weighted blanket to the couch. It's a
20-pounder. So, are you dummying in
front of me? I do have to update that
app though. I heard a really bad thing.
Oh my god, listen, there is absolutely
always something you can do. You just
need the help of an expert. Oh, and who
would that be?
>> [snorts]
>> I am the expert.
Do you have a lit candle in there? Yeah,
it has to burn continuously so I could
read the wax. If it tunnels, that means
my sister's been lying about how she's
paying for her Jetta.
Is this a diorama of the office? Oh, is
that me? Ah, no touching.
Yes, I put a spell over the branch to
protect us from getting shut down. A
spell? That is crazy. [laughter]
Unless it's a part of your culture.
Yeah, hot girl culture.
Listen, not many people know about my
watching cabinet, but I feel super bad
for you.
Plus, I know exactly what you need to
break up Mary and Noah.
A freezing spell to cool off the
passionate wildfire of two bodies. A
passionate wildfire? That's a bit much.
>> Um, you're giving Delulu lemon. Um, so
all you need to do is wrap a red string
around a photo of Noah to tie him to
your heart. Then we place the photo in
the freezer and it will cool off his
feelings for Mary.
Oh, that's easy. I'm never doing that.
My god, you sound exactly like my
sister. The fun one or the pretty one?
The annoying one.
Look, I might be a little Delulu, but
I'm not like at casting magic spells
yet.
>> no, I miss you. I miss you way more.
I can't. No, I'm at work. All right,
that's one kiss.
So, do I need a wand?
>> [music]
[music]
>> Happy K-dog. What are you, like 30?
What? Ew, no. I'm 24.
If I was turning 30, I'd literally kill
myself.
I guess I should kill myself twice.
>> [laughter]
>> Well, you work at the DMV, so your life
is basically over.
Good to know. Who did this?
>> [clears throat]
>> Who would draw Huey holding two big
rocket ships? Rockets? I
Those aren't rockets.
Those are big, hard rockets. Mm. This
doesn't make any sense. Does someone
want to blast you into space? I mean,
he's gripping onto these things for dear
life. Who drew these? Maybe the same
person who did those.
Who's the culprit?
Step forward.
Aha. This isn't over.
Cuz uh nobody's going to make an ass out
of Big Sack.
>> [laughter]
>> This is some of your finest work. Aw.
Gratitude. But I can't take credit. My
rockets have a signature curve.
Hey.
The the the the asset is in the vault.
>> [laughter]
>> Oh, you printed the photo off of Noah's
Instagram?
Come on. Relax, weirdo, okay? Take it
out. Come on.
You need to tie this binding string
around it to tie him to your heart.
Then we're going to pop it in the
freezer after. He's going to be so cold
in there.
Oh, was that the spell? Do I need to
repeat it? No.
Oh.
Okay.
Done. Okay.
Just going to pop him behind this
9-year-old box of baking soda.
Now what do I do? Now we wait for the
spell to work its magic.
Yeah, okay.
Thought we're having fun.
All good.
Ice cream cake's melting. Got to put it
in the freezer.
>> What? No, no, no. I would love some ice
cream cake.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay, maybe just take a slice. [music]
No.
>> I'm I'm very hungry. Thank you. Oh.
That's just what my body needed. Oh my
god. Is this what getting old is like?
What is this?
Why is everyone using the freezer today?
Why? Why would anyone do this?
>> I mean why does anybody do anything?
Like why did I just eat so much ice
cream cake if I'm lactose intolerant?
Maybe it's menopause.
>> Oh, thank you Grayson.
Hey, this
this creepy little red string. Why is it
tied around my neck like it's trying to
choke me?
>> I know, I really don't think it's that.
I think we should consider other
explanations like maybe it's a festive
neck scarf or a mini lanyard or a
cravat, you fancy boy. The point is we
just don't know, okay?
>> No, no, no, no, no. What? Oh no, I can't
I can't I can't be.
Back in New Zealand I dated this girl
Janine. Ew. And when I broke up with her
she became like full on obsessed. Can
you imagine? I never imagine anything
about you ever. She started following me
around and leaving me weird messages
like this. It went on for months. I had
to get a restraining order.
Do you think she followed me to the
States? That's it.
It's Genie.
>> Janine, it's Genie.
>> Yeah, it's one of those two, definitely.
>> Okay, okay. Well, I'm going to check
back home and see if anyone's heard from
her.
Wait, Noah.
Find her.
I'm a bad guy.
Oh, well.
What you up to, Barb? On that camp girl
grind? I'm making sure the Rocket Bundle
doesn't strike again. So, that's a
surveillance camera in the employee
area? Yeah. I mean, we already have them
out front and in the waiting room.
Now, we're going full Big Brother, boys.
Barb, this is an invasion of privacy.
How do you think I feel, Greg? These are
my cameras from my house. Now, I'm not
going to know what my cats are doing.
Barb, it's just a prank. It's defacement
of DMV property and an insult to the men
and women of the space program. The
camera stay up.
Unless
one of you would like to confess.
I don't know.
>> [clears throat]
>> Well, until someone does, I will be
watching you as closely as my doctor is
watching my cholesterol.
And he is concerned.
Okay, Vic. I can't take my secret chair
naps with Big Barb watching. I told you
I didn't do it. Please. Plus, I feel for
Barb. I use my cat cam to check on
Weezie.
Look at that. She's bushed. We had a
crazy game of laser chase last night.
Dude, why are you so convinced that it's
me? Maybe it's you, Greg. Yeah, sure.
You are the only person in this whole
building capable of that juvenile
behavior.
>> Okay. Name one juvenile thing that I've
ever done. Sloppy salmon, cup of farts,
bowl of boogers, ham in the fax machine.
You really think that little of me?
Yeah, kind of.
>> [snorts]
>> Wow.
Okay.
Thanks, Greg.
And BTW,
it's a jar
of farts.
A cup?
We just let them out.
Ma'am, you got to take the sunglasses
off. The government doesn't really care
about your signature look. Sorry,
official DMV business.
I love the I love the glasses.
Noah thinks that there's some crazy girl
out there who's obsessed with him. Mhm,
found her. The freezer photo is a
disaster, Sassy. He found the photo. Now
he thinks his stalker's back. Okay,
well, I've got real problems to deal
with. If Barb keeps putting up these
security cameras to spy on us, I'm not
going to be able to finish my class.
What class? Oh, I'm getting my real
estate license so I can be on Selling
Sunset.
Last week we learned location, location.
This week location, location, location.
I thought you wanted to be a pastry
chef. Mhm, no, I kept losing my nails in
the fondant. Oh. Hey, Noah. Hey. You
feeling better? Uh no, but I got the
keys to the security closet so I'm going
to check the footage for any signs of
Janine and a forehead with my name
tattooed on it.
This is great.
>> This is terrible. No, if Noah thinks his
stalker is back, you're off the hook.
But he looks so worried. He's going to
waste his entire lunch hour looking
through footage. I feel so guilty.
I've got a candle for that.
And can you scram, little one? Go look
at the second hottest girl in the
office. That's what I'm doing. Hot
Kristen went to the bathroom.
Excuse me?
Look at old Huey.
Just begging for it in this one. Yeah,
it's like they draw them with the rocket
ships and then remove them.
And this beaut's perfectly located out
of frame from Barb's cameras. Yeah, it's
like a blind spot between two prison
watchtowers. Solid nap country.
I'm going to set up a stakeout to catch
the real culprit and when I do, you're
going to feel so terrible for falsely
accusing me. Really? Mhm. Well, maybe
I'll join you. Sounds good. Great. We'll
catch him together.
Fine.
>> [music]
>> Now we just wait for the perp to come
into view.
Yep.
Who could it be?
>> [music]
[music]
>> Hey. Hey Clete. What's up?
I know you're worried, so I just wanted
to tell you this exact same thing
happened to me and it ended up being
totally fine. Someone tied a red piece
of string around a picture of you and
put it in the freezer in the break room
at your place of business? Yes. Ish.
Details were a little different, but
point is no need to stress, so
let's go get smoothies at the Chevron. I
can't. Oh, I'm sorry. I I'm just really
worried Janine is back. She's not.
Who else would do this? Oh, I don't
know. Maybe just some poor random girl
who had a brief lapse in otherwise
pretty spectacular judgement.
Spitballing here, maybe she or he, let's
be inclusive, was attracted to you and
then made the mistake of listening to a
co-worker's advice and now is filled
with
buckets of regret. Spitball complete.
Clete, do you know something about this?
Me? N- No, no. My god, it was you.
Janine made me do it.
Look.
Wait.
Look, she's here. Carrying the red
string. Why? Why? Why would do
something like this?
This is really uh
hard for me to say, Noah, but um
Sissy's in love with you.
So, no, no peace signs.
No, no finger hearts, either. Can Enough
with the fingers. What are you doing?
Put your hands down.
Hi. Hi. Hi. Hi. Hi. Hi. Hi. Good news,
uh Noah no longer thinks that his
stalker ex-girlfriend is back. Yeah, I
wasn't really worried about that. We we
we do have un poco de issue though. Uh,
he now thinks that you're in love with
him. Which is crazy, right? It's because
I told him that that that you're in love
with him. You are so lucky that I am on
my healing journey because otherwise it
would be hoops off right now. If he knew
it was me, it would ruin any chance I
have with him. And then you guys
couldn't go to the farmers market
together to buy a frugal mom. I don't
sound like that. Oh my god, I do.
Okay, you know what? Mhm?
I got you.
But you need to do something for me.
Literally anything. Please be easy.
Please be easy. Please be easy. Tell
everyone it was you who drew the rocket
winners. On the posters?
Why? What do you care? Uh, hello.
No classes means no real estate license
and that means no selling Sunset, which
means no dating one of the tiny little
billionaires.
Everyone's going to think I'm like a
pervert. Well, would you rather be a
pervert or have Noah think you were his
stalker? Why are those my choices? Hm.
Fine. You got yourself a deal, hermana.
Mhm. You're doing the white girl thing.
Not the same. Nope. Got you. Bye.
>> [music]
>> Oh, no, you struck again. We missed it.
Wow, you are unbelievable. The lengths
you'll go to deny that it's you. What?
Is there something on Something on my
face?
Oh, you think I drew this on my own face
while I was asleep? No. I think you
waited for me to fall asleep because you
saw it was the perfect alibi for you to
draw a rocket on your own face.
>> That's crazy.
Insane crazy. And I'll have you know I
draw my rockets uncircumcised.
You know what? You're just like Mrs.
Richards. Oh, Mrs. Richards, the person
whose name you haven't mentioned in all
the years we worked together.
>> Well, if you had ever listened to me,
you'd know that Mrs. Richards was my
super smoking hot sixth grade teacher,
and she blamed me for letting out
hundreds of crickets in the library. You
know what? It was Toby Stevens who did
that, and I don't know who did this.
Oh my god. They went from raccoons to
humans. This stops now. EVERYBODY,
CONFERENCE ROOM. I NEED AN AFTERNOON
EMERGENCY DUMP. A BIG OLD DUMP.
LET'S GO. GREAT.
Oh
Need some help? Yes, please.
>> Okay.
Yeah. Hey Noah, Okay. What else is I'm
just
Sessy, is there something you would like
to say to Noah?
Sure. Mhm.
I, Sessy, put your photo in the freezer
as part of a love spell because I am
madly in love with you.
Okay.
Um I collect she tipped me off and
>> Yes, I am
so head over heels.
It is my dream to become nothing other
than Mrs.
Sessy
New Zealand.
>> Wow. Look, I'm flattered. I truly am,
but I'm so sorry. I I am with Mary. For
now. To be completely honest,
you're not really my type. What the hell
did you just say to me? I see
>> just say that I'm not your type? Have
you ever I'm sorry. Do you wear glasses?
You're upset. I [sighs]
I'm so upset. I am It's just really hard
for me to hear.
>> It's all right. It's interesting.
Thank you.
>> I hate you. Okay. Oh, we got to stop
work for this and folks are mad. Nobody
leaves this room until the poster
culprit steps forth.
Wait.
Oh, Collette.
>> Ew. Don't you have something you would
like to share with everyone?
Hey everybody.
Um, it was me who drew the rocket ships.
I love me some rocket ships. I can't get
enough. No way. See, I told you it
wasn't me. Please, Collette didn't do
it. She's hardly ever seen a rocket ship
in her whole life. Uh, yes I have, Greg.
I've seen four and felt six. Uh, at the
Air and Space Museum? Okay, let's be for
real. It's obviously the culprit. Yes,
and I'm I'm sick and tired of everyone
accusing me. Am I a bit of a prankster?
Sure. Rocket ships. I'M OBSESSED WITH
THEM.
>> [screaming]
>> YOU KNOW WHAT? WE'RE GOING TO SETTLE
THIS. EVERYONE GET up and go to the
whiteboard and draw a rocket ship right
now. That's right. Big rockets, JUST
LIKE THE POSTERS. I'M TALKING FILLED UP
AND READY TO BLAST. GET UP.
OH MY GOD. Are you seriously going to
let Barb make everyone go up there and
draw a penis?
They're what?
They're penises, Barb. Yeah.
Markers, put the markers down. Put them
down. EVERYBODY GET BACK TO WORK.
I hope you're happy.
>> I am.
Hey, Collette. I just Yeah. I'm so sorry
I freaked out about the Janine of it
all. Oh. I'm a bit embarrassed about
that, so. Oh, why do you feel
embarrassed? Because I want you to think
I'm cool and I think that you're all
cool, so.
Yeah. You think that I'm cool? I do.
yeah. Of course.
Back to work? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Three, two, one, blast off!
I'm going to be an astronaut.
Oh. They were rockets.
I could have been wrong here.
You think?
I'm sorry.
How can I make it up to you?
Let me draw a rocket on your face.
No.
Ah.
Don't ask. [music]
Great job, kid.
Okay, little me.
Where do we want to go next?
Oh, hell and hearing. Oh my god, Barb.
SHOOTS AND LADDERS, THAT WAS WEIRD.
Come on, nowhere.
You're too good, Bruja.
You're too good.
>> [music]
[music]